[{"answer": "It's 147 over 89.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "How high?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "Not enough.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "How many push-ups can you do?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "I guess I wanted to see him win.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Why didn't you?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Playing mean every week -- I mean does that bring you joy?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "And I -- and I'm getting kind of worried that we're all going to have some kind of a society that has a narcissistic disorder, you know?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Well, you know, part of the reason I wanted you to act -- to join us tonight was to talk about how wonderfully you have aged, all right?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "If you're just talking about pragmatic things, I like to hike.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "What's the secret?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "This deep psychic wound you refer to, is this the powerlessness you felt during your father's illness?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "You have suggestions for that.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Sleep?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Can I tell you that the moment I turned 50, I walked into my morning coffee shop and I -- you know, I never celebrate my birthdays.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Do you find yourself in a happy place?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Yes, for the most part.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Do you think you're active for 30 minutes a day?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Do you floss your teeth?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "I love my dentist.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Not as much as I should.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Do you take -- do you take supplements?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "And did he have any other neurologic issues besides that?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Hell, no.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Do you take time to yourself?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Not enough.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "How many pushups can you do?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Um-hmm.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Someone our age ought to be able to stand on one foot -- go on one foot, OK?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Yes, later in the show, we're going to walk you through dreams -- why so many of us aren't having the right kinds, so all are troubled by the dreams that we have.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "-- oh, God, they're incredibly vivid and they don't stop, which must mean that I'm not having a certain quality of sleep, is that correct?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Oh, I remember that day.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Wasn't that fabulous?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "It was so cold.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "You were smashed?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "AUPER: Really?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "How old does your lungs or your brain think you are?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I was doing work, you know, meet and greeting and looking like a painting.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Just doing stuff?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, I was so busy working then that I couldn't think.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "So if you could give advice to that young dancing girl we just saw, what would you tell her?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Are you ready?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Or a pen?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "(INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "-- you like that?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes, well, sometimes.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "All right, do you get your blood pressure checked annually?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "AUPER: It usually sits around -- I don't know, 60 to 80 below or above.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Do you know your blood pressure?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Yes, when I go to the dentist.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Do you have doctors look in your mouth at all?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "-- it's representative of the globalization of medicine.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "A new mom?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Three, yes, my daughter Leila (ph) and my son Emmitt (ph).", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "And you have another one that's three?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "You know, it's -- it's pretty amazing.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "And go back to -- to being your old self?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Well, let me ask you a question.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "You -- you took the real age test, right?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "About five years ago.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "You have?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "My real age is 37.9 or something.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Z: Well, what's your real age?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "I didn't feel nervous.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Were you nervous about getting pregnant that late?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Every day, I have two breakfasts.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "What's a typical breakfast you might have?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "I put drops in my eyes when I'm traveling because I have to keep them moist.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "What do you do to protect your eyes?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "I thought I didn't, but I think I do.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Do you have mommy brain at all?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Not all things, but we're specifically talking about Ambien type drugs.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "You did research and that's true, that men digest quicker than women?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "You're tired.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Think about it, what is sleep really telling you?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "I am not a great sleeper.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "And are you a good sleeper?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "You'll dream of something that then happens in real life?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "I try -- this is such an old lady thing.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "What do you do to sleep better?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "No question.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "Sleep is actually fine.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "How is sleep for you?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "In fact, when I was pregnant with my daughter, I would carry ear plugs with me in my car.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 780, "question": "A power nap?", "qSentId": 779}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "You never got arrested?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "I sometimes take melatonin.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "Question for all three of you, do any of you take sleep medications?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "Because -- but you know, a natural doc told me once to take 20 milligrams of it, up to 20.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 789, "question": "Melatonin?", "qSentId": 788}, {"answer": "Toothpaste have other things in them, but I don't know if -- I haven't seen it in there.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "Toothpaste?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "I don't think about them.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "Do you keep track of these different things in literature, Madeleine?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "Are you worried about that?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "Z: It's a chemical compound that is linked to all kinds of bad stuff, including cancer.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 885, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 884}, {"answer": "It's rational to think.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 894, "question": "Like is there -- can you -- is that safe to think or is that crazy to think?", "qSentId": 893}, {"answer": "It's funny.", "docId": "130301pmt", "aSentId": 911, "question": "How does that -- Lisa, how does it make you feel younger or live longer?", "qSentId": 910}]